export const Question = [
{
    prompt: "What colour is a live wire?",
    A: "Red",
    B: "Brown",
    C: "Both",
    answer: "C",
},
{
    prompt: "What colour is a neutral wire?",
    A: "Black",
    B: "Both",
    C: "Blue",
    answer: "B",
},
{
    prompt: "What is the colour of an earth wire?",
    A: "Green",
    B: "has no color",
    C: "Green with yellow strip",
    answer: "C",
},
{
    prompt: "What happens when the live wire touches the earth wire?",
    A: "You explode!",
    B: "It triggers the earth leakage",
    C: "The wires melt after afew minutes",
    answer: "B",
},
{
    prompt: "What voltage is supplied to a domestic household in South Africa?",
    A: "400V",
    B: "12V",
    C: "230V",
    answer: "C",
},
{
    prompt: "What type of current is used in a domestic household?",
    A: "Direct Current",
    B: "Alternating Current",
    C: "Changing Current",
    answer: "B",
},
{
    prompt: "What happens if you touch both live and neutral wires at the sametime?",
    A: "You will be electrocuted",
    B: "You will suffer a light shock",
    C: "You can become blind",
    answer: "A",
},
{
    prompt: "When do you need an earth wire?",
    A: "When the object has metal exposed parts",
    B: "When the object has plastic covers",
    C: "Just put it there as a precaution",
    answer: "A",
},
{
    prompt: "Why is it important to have the wiring colour coded?",
    A: "To identify the wiring to understand the what each one represents according to international standards",
    B: "Because we can choose our own colours to make it look better",
    C: "Incase the numbers fade off the wire",
    answer: "A",
},
{
    prompt: "Is it good practice to install your main supply near a water pipe in the a wall?",
    A: "It would save space",
    B: "No, water and electricity cannot be installed near each other",
    C: "Does not matter as long as it works",
    answer: "B",
},
]
